</noscript><div class="system-alerts\_sysAlerts\_\_KCb9L"><div class="container"></div></div><div class="base\_layout\_wrapper\_\_6D1bX"><header class="header\_wrapper\_header\_\_XU\_Oq "><div class="header\_header\_\_wrapper\_\_\_HV4N"><div class="container"><div class="header\_header\_\_w2BOs"><a class=" linker\_link\_\_DFzUa linker\_link\_wrapper\_\_28QhG " aria-label="logo" href="/"><div class="header\_header\_\_left\_\_VvAHs"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="15" height="20" fill="none" viewBox="0 0 15 20"><path fill="#fff" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M0 0h12.143L15 2.857v5.714L3.571 20H0z" clip-rule="evenodd" opacity="0.45"></path><path fill="url(#a)" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M3.571 0 15 11.429v5.714L12.143 20H0V0z" clip-rule="evenodd" opacity="0.8"></path><defs><linearGradient id="a" x1="7.5" x2="7.5" y1="0" y2="20" gradientUnits="userSpaceOnUse"><stop stop-color="#FFD50B"></stop><stop offset="1" stop-color="#FFBA08"></stop></linearGradient></defs></svg><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="644" height="76" fill="none" viewBox="0 0 644 76" class="header\_header\_\_logo\_\_text\_\_IRFt2"><path fill="#fff" d="M0 1.826h28.396q4.948 0 9.895.71 5.055.608 9.036 2.636 3.98 1.927 6.453 5.477t2.474 9.432q0 6.086-3.657 10.143-3.55 3.955-9.465 5.68v.202q3.765.507 6.776 2.028 3.12 1.42 5.27 3.753 2.26 2.23 3.442 5.274 1.184 3.042 1.184 6.49 0 5.68-2.582 9.534-2.58 3.752-6.669 6.086-4.087 2.332-9.25 3.347a51.3 51.3 0 0 1-10.11 1.014H0zm16.78 28.702h12.154q1.935 0 3.764-.406 1.936-.405 3.442-1.318a6.6 6.6 0 0 0 2.367-2.434q.968-1.522.968-3.652 0-2.23-1.076-3.65a6.43 6.43 0 0 0-2.581-2.334q-1.614-.81-3.657-1.115a20.4 20.4 0 0 0-3.98-.406H16.779zm0 29.716h15.058q1.935 0 3.872-.406 2.043-.405 3.657-1.42a7.8 7.8 0 0 0 2.582-2.636q1.075-1.623 1.075-3.956 0-2.535-1.398-4.057-1.29-1.622-3.335-2.434a18.2 18.2 0 0 0-4.41-1.115 35 35 0 0 0-4.41-.305H16.78zM144.716 45.944q0 6.39-2.044 11.765t-6.131 9.33q-3.98 3.956-10.003 6.187-6.024 2.23-13.875 2.231-7.96 0-13.983-2.231t-10.11-6.187q-3.981-3.956-6.024-9.33-2.044-5.376-2.044-11.765V1.826h16.78v43.51q0 3.346 1.075 6.186 1.183 2.84 3.227 4.97 2.043 2.028 4.84 3.245 2.904 1.116 6.239 1.116t6.131-1.116q2.796-1.217 4.84-3.245a14.5 14.5 0 0 0 3.119-4.97q1.183-2.84 1.183-6.187V1.825h16.78zM170.768 1.826h16.779v71.806h-16.779zM214.211 1.826h16.78v57.201h31.084v14.605h-47.864zM282.093 1.826h25.17q9.142 0 17.317 1.927 8.282 1.926 14.413 6.288 6.13 4.26 9.68 11.156 3.657 6.897 3.657 16.735 0 8.722-3.549 15.415a33.54 33.54 0 0 1-9.358 11.157q-5.916 4.462-13.66 6.795t-16.242 2.333h-27.428zm16.78 57.201h8.712q5.809 0 10.756-1.116 5.055-1.115 8.713-3.65 3.657-2.638 5.7-6.796 2.152-4.26 2.152-10.345 0-5.273-2.152-9.128-2.043-3.955-5.593-6.49t-8.39-3.753q-4.732-1.32-10.003-1.319h-9.895zM412.111 19.371q-2.043-2.433-5.593-3.55-3.443-1.215-6.561-1.216-1.828 0-3.765.405t-3.657 1.319q-1.72.81-2.796 2.231-1.077 1.42-1.076 3.448 0 3.246 2.581 4.97 2.582 1.725 6.454 2.941 3.98 1.218 8.497 2.434 4.518 1.217 8.39 3.449a19.34 19.34 0 0 1 6.561 5.983q2.582 3.754 2.582 10.041 0 5.984-2.367 10.447a21.3 21.3 0 0 1-6.453 7.403q-3.98 2.942-9.358 4.361-5.271 1.42-11.186 1.42-7.422 0-13.768-2.13t-11.832-6.896l11.94-12.374q2.58 3.245 6.453 5.072 3.98 1.724 8.175 1.724 2.044 0 4.087-.406 2.151-.507 3.765-1.42 1.72-.912 2.689-2.333 1.075-1.42 1.075-3.347 0-3.245-2.689-5.07-2.582-1.927-6.561-3.246a214 214 0 0 0-8.605-2.637q-4.625-1.318-8.605-3.55a20.8 20.8 0 0 1-6.668-5.882q-2.582-3.651-2.582-9.635 0-5.781 2.366-10.142a23.2 23.2 0 0 1 6.454-7.303q4.087-2.94 9.358-4.36A39 39 0 0 1 400.279 0q6.455 0 12.477 1.724a29.3 29.3 0 0 1 10.864 5.781zM513.69 1.826h16.779v71.806H513.69zM561.582 37.729q0-8.621 3.011-15.62 3.12-6.997 8.605-11.866 5.485-4.97 13.015-7.606Q593.742 0 602.67 0q8.927 0 16.456 2.637 7.53 2.637 13.015 7.606 5.486 4.868 8.497 11.867 3.12 6.997 3.12 15.619 0 8.62-3.12 15.618-3.011 6.999-8.497 11.968-5.485 4.868-13.015 7.505-7.529 2.637-16.456 2.637-8.928 0-16.457-2.637-7.53-2.637-13.015-7.505-5.485-4.97-8.605-11.968-3.011-6.998-3.011-15.618m17.424 0q0 5.07 1.614 9.33a22.4 22.4 0 0 0 4.84 7.303q3.119 3.042 7.422 4.767 4.41 1.724 9.788 1.724t9.68-1.724q4.41-1.725 7.529-4.767a21.1 21.1 0 0 0 4.733-7.303q1.72-4.26 1.721-9.33 0-4.97-1.721-9.23-1.614-4.26-4.733-7.302-3.119-3.144-7.529-4.868-4.302-1.724-9.68-1.724t-9.788 1.724q-4.303 1.724-7.422 4.868-3.12 3.043-4.84 7.302-1.614 4.26-1.614 9.23M475.96 66.75a8.706 8.706 0 1 1-17.413 0 8.707 8.707 0 1 1 17.413 0"></path></svg></div></a><div class="header\_header\_\_right\_\_ltcne"></div></div></div></div></header><section class="section-notifications\_notifications\_\_x7KkA"></section><main class="base\_layout\_main\_content\_\_rA9uj "><div class="container"><div class="article-content\_article\_\_FAFom" style="margin-bottom:112px"> <h1> Privacy Policy </h1> <blockquote> <p>Your privacy is&nbsp;important to&nbsp;us. We&nbsp;have prepared this Privacy Policy to&nbsp;explain how we&nbsp;collect, use, protect, and disclose Personal Information and Usage Data when you use the BuildStore services (&laquo;Service&raquo;). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information and your preferences.</p> <p>This Privacy Policy may be&nbsp;revised from time to&nbsp;time. By&nbsp;using the Service, you agree to&nbsp;be&nbsp;bound and to&nbsp;abide by&nbsp;the most recent version of&nbsp;this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on&nbsp;Dec&nbsp;12, 2019.</p> </blockquote> <h2> GDPR compliance </h2> <p> BuildStore is&nbsp;a&nbsp;data controller and processor under the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation, &laquo;GDPR&raquo;). BuildStore has adopted the following Policy concerning protection of&nbsp;personal information in&nbsp;accordance with the GDPR. BuildStore will respond promptly to&nbsp;any requests concerning BuildStore users&rsquo; rights to&nbsp;the protection of&nbsp;personal information. </p> <h2> California Consumer Privacy Act notice </h2> <p>As&nbsp;of&nbsp;January&nbsp;1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of&nbsp;2018 (&laquo;CCPA&raquo;) provides California residents (&laquo;Consumer(s)&raquo;) certain rights with respect to&nbsp;their personal information, as&nbsp;this term is&nbsp;defined under the CCPA. In&nbsp;addition to&nbsp;the rights we&nbsp;state under this Policy and subject to&nbsp;the exceptions found under the CCPA, Consumers have the right&nbsp;to:</p> <br /> <ul> <li>Opt out of&nbsp;selling of&nbsp;their personal information should we&nbsp;sell their personal information;</li> <li>Be&nbsp;informed of&nbsp;certain details regarding our collection and use of&nbsp;their personal information;</li> <li>Request to&nbsp;delete certain personal information we&nbsp;collected from them;</li> <li>Appoint an&nbsp;agent to&nbsp;exercise their rights under the CCPA, provided that a&nbsp;duly executed notarized power of&nbsp;attorney is&nbsp;presented and provided that the agent has information deemed sufficient to&nbsp;allow&nbsp;us to&nbsp;verify the identity of&nbsp;the Consumer in&nbsp;question and to&nbsp;locate their information in&nbsp;our systems;</li> <li>Not be&nbsp;subjected to&nbsp;discrimination for exercising these rights. We&nbsp;will not deny California residents the use of&nbsp;our service, neither will we&nbsp;provide a&nbsp;different level or&nbsp;quality or&nbsp;services for exercising any of&nbsp;their CCPA rights, unless as&nbsp;permitted under the CCPA.</li> </ul> <p>This Website does not sell nor has it&nbsp;sold in&nbsp;the past 12&nbsp;months personal information to&nbsp;third parties for monetary or&nbsp;other vested interests. We&nbsp;may, however, disclose certain personal information to&nbsp;third parties and service providers in&nbsp;order to&nbsp;enable them to&nbsp;perform certain services on&nbsp;our behalf and namely to&nbsp;make the Service work properly. Regardless, we&nbsp;respect the California residents&rsquo; right to&nbsp;exclude personal information from such sharing arrangements and to&nbsp;thereby opt out of&nbsp;any future transfer of&nbsp;their personal information.</p> <p>If&nbsp;the CCPA is&nbsp;applicable to&nbsp;you and you would like to&nbsp;record such preference, please e-mail&nbsp;us at&nbsp;<a href="mailto:legal@builds.io">legal@builds.io</a>.</p> <h2> Managing your information preferences </h2> <p> You can review, correct, update, or&nbsp;delete your personal information, as&nbsp;well as&nbsp;opt out of&nbsp;any direct marketing we&nbsp;may engage&nbsp;in, by&nbsp;writing to&nbsp;us at&nbsp;<a href="mailto:legal@builds.io">legal@builds.io.</a>. If&nbsp;you have questions or&nbsp;concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please email&nbsp;us at&nbsp;<a href="mailto:legal@builds.io">legal@builds.io</a>. </p> </div></div></main><footer class="footer\_wrapper\_footer\_\_imgZw "><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_HBVhF "><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_wrapper\_\_rZfNh container"><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_left\_\_uKzDd">© BuildStore <!-- -->2024</div><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_right\_\_GVAqQ"><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_icon\_\_pMDot"><a href="https://www.facebook.com/buildstoreng" class=" linker\_link\_\_DFzUa linker\_link\_wrapper\_\_28QhG " target="\_blank" aria-label="facebook" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" data-testid="Linker-external-link-body"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="16" height="16" fill="none" viewBox="0 0 16 16"><path fill="#fff" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M0 8.045C0 12.022 2.889 15.329 6.667 16v-5.778h-2V8h2V6.222c0-2 1.288-3.11 3.111-3.11.577 0 1.2.088 1.777.177v2.044h-1.022c-.978 0-1.2.489-1.2 1.112V8h2.134l-.356 2.222H9.333V16C13.111 15.33 16 12.023 16 8.045 16 3.62 12.4 0 8 0S0 3.62 0 8.045" clip-rule="evenodd"></path></svg></a></div><div class="footer-bottom\_footerBottom\_\_icon\_\_pMDot"><a href="https://twitter.com/builds\_io/" class=" linker\_link\_\_DFzUa linker\_link\_wrapper\_\_28QhG " target="\_blank" aria-label="twitter" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" data-testid="Linker-external-link-body"><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="16" height="16" fill="none" viewBox="0 0 16 16"><path fill="#fff" d="M16 8c0 4.42-3.58 8-8 8s-8-3.58-8-8 3.58-8 8-8 8 3.58 8 8m-9.464 4.22c3.548 0 5.488-2.94 5.488-5.488q.001-.127-.004-.248c.376-.272.704-.612.964-1a4 4 0 0 1-1.108.304c.4-.24.704-.616.848-1.068-.372.22-.784.38-1.224.468a1.929 1.929 0 0 0-3.284 1.76A5.47 5.47 0 0 1 4.24 4.932c-.164.284-.26.616-.26.968 0 .668.34 1.26.86 1.604a1.9 1.9 0 0 1-.872-.24v.024A1.93 1.93 0 0 0 5.516 9.18a1.9 1.9 0 0 1-.872.032 1.93 1.93 0 0 0 1.8 1.34 3.88 3.88 0 0 1-2.856.796c.844.552 1.86.872 2.948.872"></path></svg></a></div></div></div></div></footer><div class="cookie\_popup\_cookie\_\_v5OtV "><div class="container cookie\_popup\_cookie\_\_inner\_\_u0lpa"><div><div class="cookie\_popup\_cookie\_\_title\_\_ywyN1">We use cookies</div><div class="cookie\_popup\_cookie\_\_descr\_\_n9Eyn">This helps us get to know you better and improve our site</div></div><div><button class="buttons\_button\_\_DLxHN buttons\_button\_fillViolet\_\_cAF0l " style="width:183px;min-width:183px" type="button" data-testid="button-element"><span class="buttons\_button\_\_text\_\_hj85v" style="text-transform:uppercase" data-testid="button-children">ACCEPT</span></button></div></div></div></div></div><script id="\_\_NEXT\_DATA\_\_" type="application/json">{"props":{"pageProps":{}},"page":"/legal/privacy-policy","query":{},"buildId":"AHOOV8RA\_RfFQzN2CPl8i","nextExport":true,"autoExport":true,"isFallback":false,"dynamicIds":\[62877\],"scriptLoader":\[\]}</script></body></html>
